#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nandini-sethenv-sp-87012148 (LinkedIn) coe.uno.edu/meric/ (Company)

Top Skills
Urban Design
Urban Planning
Planning for Hazard Mitigation

# Nandini Seth, ENV SP

Urban and Regional Planner

**United States** 

### Summary

Experienced Urban Planning Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the architecture & planning industry. Skilled in Policy Analysis, Land Use, Urban Design, Economic Development, and Zoning. Strong program and project management professional with a Master's degree focused in Urban Studies/Affairs from University of New Orleans.

## Experience

Office of Commissioner Lesley Briones, Precinct 4
Senior Planner
May 2023 - Present (6 months)
United States

Harris County Engineering Department

3 years 6 months

Planner/Project Manager at Community Resilience and Transportation Planning

November 2022 - May 2023 (7 months)

Planner at Platting divison December 2019 - November 2022 (3 years)

Houston, Texas, United States

City of Kenner
Capital Projects Coordinator
June 2018 - December 2018 (7 months)

Jefferson Parish Government
Planner II
July 2015 - March 2018 (2 years 9 months)

Jefferson Parish Government

Center for Hazards Assessment, Response and Technology

Graduate Research Assistant August 2012 - August 2013 (1 year 1 month)

- -Generate Repetitive Flood Loss Area Analysis;
- -Flood Claims data analysis and interpretation of Flood Insurance Rate Maps(FIRM);
- -Community outreach through informational meetings and public presentation;
- -Updating existing analysis according to the 2013 CRS Manual requirements to help the parishes earn credits.

Office of U.S Senator Mary Landrieu Project Intern June 2012 - September 2012 (4 months) Greater New Orleans Area

- Research on Improvement of Historically Underutilized Business Zone (HUB Zone) in the Federal city (Algiers, LA) to facilitate small business in urban and rural communities:
- Constituent Correspondence;
- Public Outreach

#### Education

University of New Orleans

Master's degree, Urban Studies/Affairs · (2010 - 2014)

The Maharaja Sayajirao University of Baroda Master's degree, English Language and Literature/Letters · (2004 - 2009)